four asks the following pair of
structures are identical enantiomers
diamer and constitutional isomers so we
have some straight chain alkanes with
bromo groups on them and why don't we go
ahead and number these parent chains so
on the left which direction would we
number this we would start from the
right and we would get 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
so that is an octane and then on the
right this one we would number from left
to right because that will give the
bromine occurring soonest 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
8 so where are the bromo groups over
here they're on carbons three and five
and then on the other structure they're
on carbons 2 and four so these are
actually completely different molecules
these are not stereoisomers these are
constitutional isomers they have
different connectivity remember that
stereoisomer have